&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：现在我的论点是，即使你可以同时做这两件事
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Now my argument is that even though you could do both of these
使用let时，您应该只使用let来执行for循环上的变量。
with let, you should only do the variable on the for loop with let.
如果有属于函数整个作用域的变量，
If you have a variable that belongs to the entire scope of the function,
向你的读者发出信号的正确句法方式是不要
the correct syntactic way to signal that to your reader is not to
在函数范围的顶层使用let，但是
use a let at the top level of your function scope, but
使用var是因为24年来一直在做的事情。
to use a var cuz that the thing it's always done for 24 years.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：如果要用let替换var online，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: If you were to replace the var online with a let,
即使在这个特定的例子中，它仍然在功能上工作。
even though in this particular example it would still functionally work.
我的论点是，它将删除少量重要的语义
My argument is that it would remove a small amount of important semantic
来自读者的信息，因为读者不会知道，
information from the reader, because the reader would then not know,
那你的意图是什么？
well what is your intent?
你的意图是让我在任何地方都使用它，还是你的意图是
Is your intent for me to use it everywhere or is your intent for
我只能在这里使用最顶端的功能吗？
me to only use here at the very top of the function?
我真的不知道，因为我们应该发出一个非常
I don't really know, because lets are supposed to signal a very
变量的本地化使用，理想情况下只需几行代码。
localized usage of a variable, ideally within only a couple of lines of code.
如果你想在整个函数中使用变量，
And if you're intent is to use the variable across the whole function,
let关键字可能有效，但它不是正确的工具。
the let keyword might work, but it's not the right tool.
这不是工具的正确使用。
It's not the right usage of the tool.
你以前听过这句谚语，如果你要插个螺丝，或者你要把
You've heard that adage before, if you are gonna put a screw in or you're gonna put
钉进去，你应该选择正确的工具，锤子对，好的。
a nail in, you should choose the right tool, hammer versus, all right.
但我要扩展这个类比，因为你不仅应该选择正确的工具，
But I'm gonna extend that analogy, cuz not only should you choose the right tool,
如果我有一颗钉子和一把锤子，我已经做了一些家居修理和
if I had a nail and I had a hammer, I've done some home repair and
我可以合理地把锤子放在墙上，把钉子钉在墙上，好吧。
I could probably reasonably put a hammer into a wall, put a nail into a wall, okay.
但是如果我有同样的工具，同样的钉子
But what would happen if I had the same tool and the same nail and to put
墙上的钉子，我把锤子放进嘴里，我就这么做了，(声音)。
the nail in the wall, I put the hammer in my mouth and I just did, [SOUND].
我有合适的工具来做正确的工作，但我使用工具的方式是错误的。
I have the right tool for the right job but I'm using the tool the wrong way.
光有正确的工具是不够的，
It's not enough to have the right tool,
你需要以正确的方式使用正确的工具。
you need to use the right tool the right way.
所以即使let可能是一个有用的工具，
So even though let might be a tool that would work,
它的使用方式不正确。
it's not being used in the correct way.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：这里的var关键字更适合说我有
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: The var keyword here is a more appropriate tool to say I have
应跨使用的变量。
a variable that should be used across.
这是一个思维实验，想象一下有人要设计
Here's a thought experiment, imagine somebody were to design
一种编程语言，只允许您
a programming language that only allowed you to
在函数的第一行访问函数的任何参数。
access any parameters to a function on the very first line of the function.
在第一行之外，您无法访问参数。
And beyond the first line you couldn't access the parameters.
你们中有多少人会觉得这是一门有趣的语言
How many of you would find that to be a fun language
而你们中有多少人会发现这在一门语言中是一种恼人的限制？
versus how many of you would find that to be an annoying restriction in a language?
我认为原因，这就是我想说的，就是它是自然的
I think the reason, and this is what I'm getting at, is it is natural
在代码设计中，有些东西不是块范围的。
within the design of code that some things are not block scoped.
有些东西是，如果你有自然块范围的东西，
Some things are, and if you have something that is naturally block scoped,
请使用LET。
please use let.
我不是说任何关于let的事，用let来阻止范围，
I'm not saying anything about let, use let to block scope,
这就是它的用途。
that's exactly what it's for.
但是，请不要去寻找把东西变成不是天生的let。
But please don't go looking to make things into lets that aren't naturally lets.
是？&gt；&gt；扬声器1：所以
Yes? &gt;&gt; Speaker 1: So
如果您使用ESLint，我认为默认设置是如果您使用var，
if you use ESLint, I think the default setting is that if you use var,
然后你会得到意想不到的邀请，或者反过来，对吧。
then you get the unexpected let, or the other way around, right.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：没错。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: That's true.
我只是不同意他们的观点
And I just disagree with them, and
我已经在我自己的ESLint中关闭了这个规则，好吧。
I have that rule turned off in my own ESLint, okay.
任何不允许您自定义它的工具，而是强制执行
Any tool that doesn't allow you to customize it and instead enforces
它自己对你的看法，是一个没有帮助你的工具，它在妨碍你。
its own opinion on you, is a tool that's not helping you, it's getting in your way.
我认为这并不是真的以一种有益的方式妨碍了你。
And I would argue it's not really getting in your way in a helpful way.
它在你的路上阻碍你的交流。
It's getting on your way and preventing you from communicating.
怎么了？
Yes?
&gt；&gt；Speaker 2：检查第二行，如果我们有var或let，将变量
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: To review for line two, if we have var or let, will the variable
在-&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson中以相同的方式执行函数：在此特定代码中
function in the same way in the- &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: In this particular code
片段他们的行为是一样的。
snippet they will behave the same.
所以我现在这张幻灯片上所做的就是一个文体上的论证。
So all I'm making the case right now on this exact slide is a stylistic argument.
我要做一个更大的案子来解释为什么你有时想要var，
I'm about to make a bigger case for why you sometimes want var,
但现在我只是在为var做一个文体上的论证。
but right now I'm only making a stylistic argument for var.
var的语义论证，好的。
A semantic argument for var, okay.
[咳嗽]所以如果你有一个变量会出现在
[COUGH] So if you have a variable that is going to show up in
一个地方，否则会被认为是一个街区和
a place that would otherwise be considered a block and
你使用一个let，猜猜那个变量发生了什么？
you use a let, guess what happens to that variable?
不管你想不想，它都附着在那个块上。
Whether you want it to or not, it attaches to that block.
我经常遇到的一个例子是，如果我试图使用一个let和
One of the examples that I often run across is if I'm trying to use a let and
我在try-catch块中使用它，
I use it inside of a try-catch block,
我不认为try-catch是一个块，我不认为它是一个范围。
I don't think of try-catch as a block, I don't think of it as a scope.
我认为它是一种捕获异常的句法方法，
I think of it as a syntactic way to catch exceptions,
甚至不是一个特别好的设计，但它是我们捕获异常的方式。
not even a particularly well designed one, but it is how we catch exceptions.
我当然不认为它是我隐藏范围的地方。
I certainly don't think of it as a place for me to hide scope.
但是，let关键字和
And yet, the let keyword and
const关键字块在其中自己作用域。
the const keyword block scope themselves inside of it.
所以猜猜如果我们从var到let进行全局查找和替换会发生什么？
So guess what would happen if we did our global find and replace from var to let?
这个代码会被破坏，因为在第九行没有id。
This code would break because there wouldn't be an id on line nine.
无功提升机，我们会让它重新升起，但是
Var hoists, we'll get it back to hoisting, but
var将自身附加到函数范围。
var attaches itself to the function scope.
我会在这样的情况下争辩，这可以说并不是所有的时间，但是
And I would argue in cases like this, which arguably are not all the time, but
在某些情况下，var关键字比let更可取
in some cases, the var keyword is preferable to the let
关键字，因为在这种情况下，它能够转义意外的块。
keyword because it is able, in this case, to escape an unintended block.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：这里的替代方案是在外部声明var
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: The alternative here would have been to declare a var outside
的尝试，就像我们之前做的几张幻灯片，然后在两个地方分配给它。
of the try, just like we did a few slides ago, and then assign to it in two places.
我会争辩说，你给它添加的代码行越多，
And I would argue that the more that you add lines of code to that,
你越是把声明和任务分开，它就越难
the further you separate the declaration from the assignment, the harder it is for
需要理解的人。
people to understand.
所以这是我倾向于使用var之类的东西的地方之一。
So this is one of those places where I tend to prefer using something like a var.
当我们讨论var时，var可以做的另一件事是
While we're on the topic of var, another thing that var can do which let can not is
您可以在一个作用域中多次使用var。
that you can use var more than once inside of a scope.
这里var在一个函数范围内被使用了两次，并且
Here var is being used twice within a function scope, and
我们不会有任何例外。
we're not gonna get any exceptions whatsoever.
我使用var online six是因为我试图消除歧义
And I used the var online six because I was trying to disambiguate
我的身份来自哪里。
where id comes from.
这是我发送给读者的语义信号，
This is a semantic signal that I'm sending to the reader,
不管我们走哪条路，
regardless of which path we go through,
函数作用域中会有一个id，它会有一个值。
there's gonna be an id in the function scope and it's gonna have a value.
所以我把var放在这两个地方，我可以这样做，因为var可以做到这一点。
So I put var in both places, and I can do that because that's what var can do.
我不能这么做。
I can't do that with a let.
我不经常这样做，就像我说的那样。
I don't do this that often, as again as I've said.
这并不是代码中经常发生的事情。
This is not something that happens a lot in the code.
但在发生这种情况的地方，我认为var更好
But in the places that it happens, I think that it is better that var is
然后，具有不同功能的工具确实会让。
a tool that has a different capability then does let.
如果我采用了一些完全禁止使用var的ESLint规则，
And if I had adopted some ESLint rule that completely forbid all uses of var,
在这种情况下我会受到限制。
I would be restricted in this scenario.
这里还有一个地方，我喜欢使用var来消除范围的歧义。
Here's another place where I like to use the var for the disambiguation of scope.
我倾向于我的函数长度不超过15或20行代码。
I tended to prefer my functions to be no longer than about 15 or 20 lines of code.
因为我想让我的所有功能在我的代码屏幕上一次可见，
Cuz I'd like to have all of my functions be visible on my code screen at once,
马上在我的编辑里。
in my editor at once.
但每隔一段时间，也许比我愿意承认的更频繁，
But every once in a while, maybe more often than I'd like to admit,
我的函数是100行或200行长，它确实发生了。
my functions are 100 lines or 200 lines long, it does happen.
你们中的一些人可能有一些长的功能，好吧。
Some of you probably have some long functions, okay.
如果我在函数的第一行声明某个变量
If I declare on line one of a function some variable and
它叫老师，我把它用于某种目的，我用它来
it's called teacher and I'm using it for some purpose, and I use it for
几行，然后我们向下200行，然后我需要再次使用变量。
a few lines and then we go down 200 lines and then I need to use the variable again.
如果我开始访问它并分配给它，并且
If I just start accessing it and assigning to it, and
读者一直滚动到那里，他们看到了那个老师，
the reader is scrolled all the way down there and they see that teacher,
他们不会清楚它来自什么范围。
it is not gonna be clear to them what scope it comes from.
他们怎么解决这个问题？
How are they gonna solve that?
他们得往上滚动200行然后去找一位var老师。
They're gonna have to scroll 200 lines up and go look for a var teacher.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：我喜欢在任何地方重用变量
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: What I like to do is any place where I'm going to reuse a variable
在一个显然还没有宣布的地方，
in a place where it's not obviously already having been declared,
是我重新声明它是为了让它更清楚
is I redeclare it to make it clear and
完全明确它属于什么范围。
completely unambiguous what scope it belongs to.
所以我在第200行写了另一个变量来告诉你我
So I put another var id down on line 200 to show you that I'm
在这个作用域中使用名为id的变量，
using a variable called id in this scope,
无论是只声明一次还是重新声明。
regardless of whether it was declared only once or being redeclared.
var可以在范围内重用，但不能。
Vars can be reused within a scope, lets cannot.
所以我认为var和var的原因既有语义上的原因，也有行为上的原因
So there are both semantic reasons and behavioral reasons why I think var and
我们应该在你的程序中共存，而不是让一个成为另一个。
let should coexist in your program rather than having one be the other.
事实上，我会说，基本上没有时间在所有的计算机
As a matter of fact, I would say, essentially no time in all of computer
科学史上一直都是真实的，x就是新的y。
science history has that ever really been true, that x is the new y.
这不是一件事。
That's just not a thing.
我们创造新的东西，但它几乎从来没有，在整个范围内
We create new stuff, but it almost never, in the whole scope of everything that
我们发明了，当你创造一个新的东西时，几乎从来没有这种情况
we've invented, it is almost never the case that when you create a new thing
它完全和完全地立即排除了之前的事情。
it completely and totally obviates the previous thing immediately.
它几乎总是在增加。
It's almost always that it augments.
所以我们这里有一个例子
And so what we have here is an example where
我们喜欢写博客文章，说let是新的var和
we love to write blog post that say let is the new var and
我们喜欢有这样的T恤，我们喜欢做全球搜索和
we love to have t-shirts that say that and we love to do global find and
取代，但实际上让不是新的var，它是让加var。
replaces, but in reality let is not the new var, it is let plus var.
它们都对我们的计划有用。
They both are useful for our programs.
你有问题吗？
You had a question?
&gt；&gt；扬声器1：是的，如果你，就像在这种情况下，如果你有两次id。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: Yeah, if you, like in this case, if you have id twice.
那么var是否存储在相同的内存位置或
Is then the var stored in the same memory location or
是否有两个相互引用的内存位置或？
are there two memory locations that reference each other or?
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：只有一个大理石。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Just one marble.
还记得前面的示例，当我们在第六行遇到第二个var时
Remember from our earlier example, when we run across the second var on line six
在编译阶段，我们会说，嘿，蓝色范围，
during the compilation phase, we would have said, hey blue scope,
嘿查找记录的范围，听说过这个叫id的东西吗？
hey scope of lookup record, ever heard of this thing called id?
他会说，是的，他会说，
And he would have said, yep, and he would have said,
好的酷，没什么可做的，没有行动。
okay cool, nothing to do, no op.
已经有一个叫id的大理石了。
There's already a marble called id.